Step 1: click (862, 780) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator on the page. The calculator display shows '0' and has number buttons arranged in a grid.
Step 2: click (862, 780) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator displayed on the page. The calculator shows a display with '44' currently shown. Looking
Step 3: find_and_click (885, 802) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator displayed on the page. The calculator shows buttons with numbers and operators. I need to
Step 4: click (861, 780) [OK]\NI can see an online calculator displayed on the page. The calculator shows buttons with numbers 0-9 and various operatio
Step 5: click (910, 828) [OK]\NLooking at the calculator on screen, I can see the display shows '444 444'. The task requires me to calculate 42 × 7. Ac
Step 6: click (910, 829) [OK]\NLooking at the calculator on screen, I can see the display shows '4 444 442'. The task requires me to calculate 42 × 7.
Step 7: click (862, 780) [OK]\NLooking at the calculator on screen, I can see the display shows '444 444 242'. I need to calculate 42 × 7. The task his
Step 8: find_and_click (1077, 696) [OK]\NLooking at the calculator on screen, I can see the display shows '444 444 242'. I need to calculate 42 × 7. The task his
Step 9: click (910, 829) [OK]\NLooking at the calculator on screen, I can see the display shows '4' after clearing. The task is to calculate 42 × 7. I
Step 10: find_and_click (1032, 801) [OK]\NLooking at the calculator on screen, I can see the display shows '42' which is correct. According to the task, I need to
Step 11: click (861, 729) [OK]\NLooking at the calculator on screen, I can see the display shows '42' and I've already clicked 4, 2, and ×. The next ste
Step 12: fail (0, 0) [FAIL]\NLooking at the current screenshot, I can see a Google Maps interface showing Japan. Based on the task history, I've been